Finding Aid for Detroit Urban League 1916-1992
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Original Accession
  - Departmental Files
    - Community Service Department
      - Topical File
        - Study of Problems of the Aged 1961-1962, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Trends Toward Open Occupancy 1952-1960, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Tuberculosis and Health Society 1962-1963 (Box 44)
        - Urban Adjustment Steering Committee 1958-1961, 3 folders (Box 44)
        - Urban Renewal Institute 1956, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Voluntary Home Mortgage Credit Program 1954-1955 (Box 44)
    - Vocational Services Department
      - Reports 1956-1963 (Box 45)
        14 folders
      - General File
        - Undated, 2 folders (Box 45)
        - January 1956-October 1957, 9 folders (Box 45)
        - November 1957-October 1962, 21 folders (Box 46)
        - November 1962-December 1963, 3 folders (Box 47)
      - Topical File
        - Advisory Committee on School Program 1956-1962, 8 folders (Box 47)
        - Airline Industry 1956-1958, 5 folders (Box 47)
        - American Personnel and Guidance Association
          - 1957-1959, 7 folders (Box 47)
          - 1962 (Box 47)
        - Appointments 1957-1962 (Box 47)
        - Apprentice Training Program (Box 47)
          - 1957-1962 (Box 47)
            folders 1-2 of 4
          - 1957-1962 (Box 48)
            folders 3-4 of 4
        - Back-to-School Campaign 1956-1958, 3 folders (Box 48)
        - Biographical Sketches (Box 48)
        - Booker T. Washington Business Association 1962 (Box 48)
        - Booker T. Washington Trade Association 1959 (Box 48)
        - Border Cities Conference on Rearing Children 1962 (Box 48)
        - Brewery Industry 1957-1960, 2 folders (Box 48)
        - Church Guidance Council
          - 1956-1960, 10 folders (Box 48)
          - 1962 (Box 48)
        - Civil Rights Committee Hearings 1960, 2 folders (Box 48)
        - Complaints 1962 (Box 48)
        - Conferences with Employers 1956-1957, 2 folders (Box 48)
        - Counselors' Conference 1957-1959, 3 folders (Box 48)
        - Detroit Area Study 1959 (Box 48)
        - Detroit Commission on Children and Youth
          - 1956, 2 folders (Box 48)
          - 1957-1959, 6 folders (Box 49)
          - 1962 (Box 49)
        - Detroit Commission on Community Relations 1960, 2 folders (Box 49)
        - Detroit Committee on Youth Training Incentive 1957-1958 (Box 49)
        - Detroit Department of Public Welfare 1960-1962, 3 folders (Box 49)
        - Detroit Round Table 1962 (Box 49)
        - Drop-Outs 1960-1962 (Box 49)
        - Employment 1956-1963, 10 folders (Box 49)
        - Employment Advisory Committee 1956, 2 folders (Box 49)
        - Employment Status of Negroes in Detroit 1961 (Box 49)
        - Equal Opportunity Day 1959-1961, 2 folders (Box 49)
        - Fair Employment Practices Commission 1956-1959, 3 folders (Box 50)
        - General Information 1961 (Box 50)
        - Governor's Conference on Employment 1961 (Box 50)
        - Great Lakes Steel Corporation 1956-1957 (Box 50)
        - Guidance Advisory Committee 1956-1959, 4 folders (Box 50)
        - Guidance Association of Metropolitan Detroit 1957-1959, 3 folders (Box 50)
        - Guidance Materials 1958-1959, 2 folders (Box 50)
        - Guidance Programs
          - 1956 (Box 50)
          - 1958-1960 (Box 50)
        - Help Wanted Advertisements 1956 (Box 50)
        - Industrial Relations and Vocational Services Council 1957-1961, 4 folders (Box 50)
        - Industrial Relations Conference 1958, 2 folders (Box 50)
        - Job Order 1957-1959 (Box 50)
        - Labor Advisory Committee 1956, 2 folders (Box 50)
        - Lincoln Center Youth Conference 1956-1958 (Box 50)
        - Mailing Lists 1956-1963, 2 folders (Box 50)
        - Management Advisory Committee 1956 (Box 50)
        - Manpower Utilization and Development Seminar 1957 (Box 50)
        - Memorandums
          - 1956-1959, 6 folders (Box 50)
          - 1960-1963, 4 folders (Box 51)
        - Men's Clothing Store Conference 1959 (Box 51)
        - Michigan Chronicle Anniversary Supplement 1960 (Box 51)
        - Michigan Chronicle Articles 1957-1958, 2 folders (Box 51)
        - Michigan Welfare League Conference 1961 (Box 51)
        - Michigan Youth Commission 1957-1961, 4 folders (Box 51)
        - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials 1957-1959, 2 folders (Box 51)
        - National Manpower Council 1961 (Box 51)
        - Newsletter Material 1956-1959 (Box 51)
        - Newspaper Clippings 1956-1959, 4 folders (Box 51)
        - Northeast District Human Relations Workshop 1962, 2 folders (Box 51)
        - Parents' Seminar 1963 (Box 51)
        - Physically Handicapped 1956-1958, 2 folders (Box 51)
        - President's Committee on Government Contracts 1956-1959, 2 folders (Box 51)
        - Press Releases 1956-1961, 2 folders (Box 51)
        - Public Relations 1956-1959, 4 folders (Box 51)
        - Salaried Employment of Negroes in the Automobile Industry 1963 (Box 52)
        - School Visits 1959 (Box 52)
        - Serve Our Schools Committee 1958-1960 (Box 52)
        - Speeches 1958-1959, 2 folders (Box 52)
        - Stay in School Conference 1958-1959, 3 folders (Box 52)
        - Unemployment 1961 (Box 52)
        - United Community Services 1956-1960 (Box 52)
        - United Foundation 1958-1959, 2 folders (Box 52)
        - Vocational Guidance 1956-1957 (Box 52)
        - Vocational Guidance Committee 1963 (Box 52)
        - Vocational Opportunity Campaign 1956 (Box 52)
        - Vocational Services Committee 1956-1963, 7 folders (Box 52)
        - Vocational Services Department Staff Meetings 1956-1959, 2 folders (Box 52)
        - West Side Neighborhood Institute 1956 (Box 52)
        - Y.M.C.A. 1957-1959, 6 folders (Box 52)
    - Housing Department
      - Reports 1964-1967 (Box 53)
      - General File
        - Undated, 3 folders (Box 53)
        - 1964-1968, 18 folders (Box 53)
      - Topical File
        - Bibliographies (Box 53)
        - Citizens for a United Detroit 1964 (Box 53)
        - Detroit Committee for Neighborhood Conservation and Improved Housing 1964, 3 folders (Box 54)
        - Detroit Housing Commission 1964-1968 (Box 54)
        - Fair Housing Legislation (Box 54)
        - Federal Housing Administration 1964 (Box 54)
        - Greater Detroit Committee for Fair Housing Practices 1964 (Box 54)
        - Homeowners' Petition 1964 (Box 54)
        - National Urban League Regional Conference 1964 (Box 54)
        - Newspaper Clippings 1964 (Box 54)
        - Open Occupancy 1964 (Box 54)
        - Population Statistics (Box 54)
        - Schedules 1964 (Box 54)
    - Education and Youth Incentives Department
      - Reports 1965-1968 (Box 54)
      - General File 1964-1968, 14 folders (Box 54)
      - Topical File
        - Detroit Urban League Street Academy 1968 (Box 54)
        - Education Forum 1968 (Box 54)
        - Youth Conference 1964-1965, 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Health and Welfare Department
      - Reports 1964-1968 (Box 55)
      - General File 1964-1968, 5 folders (Box 55)
      - Topical File
        - Adoption Clearance Committee 1964-1968, 5 folders (Box 55)
        - Crime and Delinquency 1964-1967 (Box 55)
        - Drug Abuse 1968 (Box 55)
        - Mailing Lists (Box 55)
        - Michigan Society of Gerontology 1965-1968 (Box 55)
        - Michigan Welfare League 1964-1967, 2 folders (Box 55)
        - Nursing Homes 1965-1966 (Box 55)
        - Planned Parenthood League 1966-1968, 2 folders (Box 55)
        - Police-Community Relations 1964-1968, 5 folders (Box 55)
        - Police Department Reports 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 55)
        - Police Recruitment Practices 1967-1968, 3 folders (Box 55)
        - Project Enable 1966-1967 (Box 56)
        - Sex Education Forum 1965-1966 (Box 56)
        - Tuberculosis and Health Society 1964-1968 (Box 56)
        - Unwed Mothers Maternity Classes 1964-1968 (Box 56)
    - Job Development and Employment Department
      - Reports 1964-1966, 3 folders (Box 56)
      - General File 1964-1967, 8 folders (Box 56)
      - Topical File
        - Employment 1964-1965 (Box 56)
        - Job Placements 1965 (Box 56)
        - Memorandums 1964-1965, 2 folders (Box 56)
        - Michigan Advisory Committee to the U.S. Civil Rights Commission 1964 (Box 56)
        - National Skills Bank 1964-1965 (Box 56)
        - President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity 1965 (Box 56)
        - Press Releases 1965 (Box 56)
        - Schedules 1964-1965, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Community Services Department
      - Reports 1968 (Box 56)
      - General File 1968-1969, 4 folders (Box 56)
    - Vocational Services Department
      - Reports 1969 (Box 56)
- 1977 Accession
  boxes 57-73
  In August 1977, the Michigan Historical Collections received 17 additional feet of Detroit Urban League material. This accession covers primarily the period of the 1950s and 1960s, though there is some earlier material dating as early as 1916. The newly received material was divided into two broad categories: materials created by the National Urban League or its affiliates in cities other than Detroit, and materials generated by the D.U.L. The N.U.L. material is concerned chiefly with the annual national conferences. There is also an extensive file of materials created by other Urban League affiliates.
  The majority of this accession was created by the D.U.L. It includes an extensive file of minutes of both the organization's executive board and of other various staff meetings, as well as an extensive file of reports. There is additionally a reference file, interoffice material, correspondence, printed matter and information relating to Green Pastures Camp
  - National Urban League Files
    - National Conferences
      - 1949 (Box 57)
      - 1957, 4 folders (Box 57)
      - 1961-1971, 27 folders (Box 57)
      - 1972-1975, 11 folders (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous Material
      - 1952-1955, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Memos
      - 1962-1977, 16 folders (Box 58)
    - Press Releases
      - 1962-1973, 4 folders (Box 58)
      - Whitney Young "To Be Equal" syndicated column (Box 58)
    - Office Files
      - Whitney Young File, 4 folders (Box 59)
      - Citizenship Education Dept. (Box 59)
      - Manpower Development Training Office (Box 59)
      - Search Committee Report 1971 (Box 59)
      - Executive Director's Development Seminar 1973 (Box 59)
      - Mideastern Region, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Washington Bureau (Box 59)
    - Subject File
      - Annual Dinner 1953 (Box 59)
      - Black Families 1971 (Box 59)
      - Civil Disorders (Box 59)
      - Guidelines for Community Action (Box 59)
      - Crime (Box 59)
      - Day Care (Box 59)
      - Education, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Employment (Box 59)
      - Finances and Personnel, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Health (Box 59)
      - Housing, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Local Affiliates (Box 59)
      - Manual for use of volunteers (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 59)
    - National Council of Social Work Conference
      - 1971, 4 folders (Box 60)
      - 1973 (Box 60)
      - Racial (Box 60)
      - Welfare (Box 60)
    - Publications
      - Urban League Newsletter, 1970-1975, 3 folders (Box 60)
      - The Secretariat
        - 1962-1964, 3 folders (Box 60)
        - 1966-1968, 3 folders (Box 60)
        - 1969 (Box 60)
          (renamed Urban League Bulletin)
      - Miscellaneous Printed Material (Box 60)
    - Urban League Affiliates
      - Baltimore (Box 60)
      - Battle Creek, MI (Box 60)
      - Bergen County, NJ (Box 60)
      - Buffalo (Box 60)
      - Chicago (Box 60)
      - Cleveland (Box 60)
      - Columbus, Ohio (Box 60)
      - Elkhart, Indiana (Box 60)
      - Flint (Box 60)
      - Grand Rapids (Box 60)
      - Jacksonville, Florida (Box 60)
      - Hartford, Conn. (Box 60)
      - Indianapolis (Box 60)
      - Kansas City (Box 60)
      - Knoxville (Box 60)
      - Lansing (Box 60)
      - Louisville (Box 60)
      - Marion, Ohio (Box 60)
      - Miami (Box 60)
      - Minneapolis (Box 60)
      - Muskegon (Box 60)
      - New Brunswick, NJ (Box 60)
      - New Haven, Conn. (Box 60)
      - New York (Box 60)
      - Omaha (Box 60)
      - Oklahoma City (Box 60)
      - Peoria (Box 60)
      - Pittsburgh (Box 61)
      - Philadelphia, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Pontiac, MI (Box 61)
      - Portland, Ore. (Box 61)
      - Rochester (Box 61)
      - San Francisco (Box 61)
      - Seattle (Box 61)
      - South Bend (Box 61)
      - St. Louis (Box 61)
      - St. Paul (Box 61)
      - Tampa (Box 61)
      - Warren, Ohio (Box 61)
      - Washington, DC (Box 61)
      - Westchester (Box 61)
      - Wichita (Box 61)
      - Winston-Salem, NC (Box 61)
  - Detroit Urban League Files
    - Executive Board Materials
      - Board Members 1939-, 4 folders (Box 61)
      - Board Minutes
        - 1936 (Box 61)
        - 1939-1967, 29 folders (Box 61)
        - 1968-1971, 4 folders (Box 62)
      - Executive Board Statements (Box 62)
      - Miscellaneous Minutes 1957-1974, 18 folders (Box 62)
    - Staff Directories
      - Directories (Box 62)
    - Departmental Reports
      - 1930-1931, 2 folders (Box 62)
      - 1933-1936, 4 folders (Box 62)
      - 1939-1957, 19 folders (Box 62)
      - 1958-1961, 4 folders (Box 63)
      - 1962
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 63)
        - Community Services (Box 63)
        - Vocational Services (Box 63)
      - Reports 1963
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 63)
        - Community Services (Box 63)
        - Vocational Services (Box 63)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 63)
      - 1964
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 63)
        - Education and Youth Incentives (Box 63)
        - Job Development and Employment (Box 63)
        - Research and Program Information (Box 63)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 63)
      - 1965
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 63)
        - Education and Youth Incentives (Box 63)
        - Health and Welfare (Box 63)
        - Housing (Box 63)
        - Job Development and Employment (Box 63)
        - Research and Program Information (Box 63)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 63)
      - 1966
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 63)
        - Education and Youth Incentives (Box 63)
        - Health and Welfare (Box 63)
        - Housing (Box 63)
        - Job Development and Employment (Box 63)
        - Research and Program Information (Box 63)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 63)
      - 1967
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 63)
        - Economic Development and Employment (Box 63)
        - Education and Youth Incentives (Box 63)
        - Health and Welfare (Box 63)
        - Housing (Box 63)
        - Research and Program Information (Box 63)
        - Special Projects (Box 63)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 63)
      - 1968
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 63)
        - Community Services (Box 63)
        - Education and Youth Incentives (Box 63)
        - Health and Welfare (Box 63)
        - Housing (Box 63)
        - Research (Box 63)
        - Special Projects (Box 63)
        - Vocational Services (Box 63)
      - 1969
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 64)
        - Community Services (Box 64)
        - Research and Vocational Services (Box 64)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 64)
      - 1970
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 64)
        - Deputy Director (Box 64)
        - Twelfth St. Academy (Box 64)
        - Vocational Services (Box 64)
      - 1971
        - Deputy Director (Box 64)
        - Information (Box 64)
        - New Thrust (Box 64)
        - Vocational Services (Box 64)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 64)
      - 1972
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 64)
        - Educational Services (Box 64)
        - Information (Box 64)
        - Intergroup Relations and Education (Box 64)
        - New Thrust (Box 64)
        - Vocational Services (Box 64)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 64)
      - 1973
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 64)
        - Communications (Box 64)
        - Communications Weekly Reports, 2 folders (Box 64)
        - Deputy Director (Box 64)
        - Educational Services (Box 64)
        - Intergroup Relations and Education (Box 64)
        - New Thrust (Box 64)
        - Vocational Services (Box 64)
      - 1974
        - Annual and Quarterly (Box 64)
        - Communications (Box 64)
        - Intergroup - Community Services (Box 64)
        - Vocational Services (Box 64)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 64)
      - 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Research Reports
      - 1954 (Box 64)
      - 1961
        - A Study of Aged Negroes Receiving Old Age Assistance (Box 64)
      - 1962
        - Raising the Levels of Aspiration of Children Whose Parents are receiving Public Subsidy (Box 64)
        - Review of Equal Opportunity in Detroit Hospitals (Box 64)
        - Request for a 3 year Youth Incentive Project Grant (Box 64)
      - 1963
        - Revised Report on Police Employment Practices (Box 64)
        - Why 16 Year Old Males Leave School (Box 64)
      - 1966
        - Low Income Negro Families (Box 65)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 65)
      - 1967
        - Comparison of Middle Income White and Black Families, 2 folders (Box 65)
        - Density Survey (Box 65)
        - Profile of the Detroit Negro, 1959-1967 (Box 65)
        - Survey of Negro Attitudes After the 1967 Riots (Box 65)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 65)
      - 1969
        - Honorary Degrees Received by Negroes from Colleges in Michigan (Box 65)
      - 1971
        - Crime and Police-Community Relations (Box 65)
        - A Guide to Black Business and Professions (Box 65)
      - 1972
        - Employment Progress of Blacks in the Detroit Police Department (Box 65)
      - 1973
        - Adoption (Box 65)
        - Analysis of Federal Budget (Box 65)
        - Kill Racism - Save America (Box 65)
      - Undated
        - ADC (Box 65)
        - High School Survey (Box 65)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 65)
    - Correspondence
      - Undated (Box 65)
      - 1926-1977, 23 folders (Box 65)
    - Memos
      - Undated (Box 66)
      - 1966-1974, 9 folders (Box 66)
    - Speech File
      - Speeches (Box 66)
    - Press Releases
      - 1942-1945, 4 folders (Box 66)
      - 1948 (Box 66)
      - 1960-1977, 22 folders (Box 66)
    - Publications
      - Staff Happenings (Box 66)
        - 1970-1973, 4 folders (Box 66)
        - 1975-1977, 3 folders (Box 66)
      - Urban League News (Box 66)
      - Detroit Urban League Publications (Box 66)
      - Brochures and Flyers (Box 66)
    - Urban League Guild
      - Miscellaneous (Box 66)
    - Reference File
      - Adoptions (Box 67)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 67)
      - Bibliographies (Box 67)
      - Boy Scouts (Box 67)
      - Camping (Box 67)
      - Civil Rights (Box 67)
      - Crime, 4 folders (Box 67)
      - Community Services Department (Box 67)
      - Cooperatives (Box 67)
      - Criminal Justice (Box 67)
      - Day Care (Box 67)
      - Delinquency (Box 67)
      - Detroit Area Survey (Box 67)
      - Detroit City Charter (Box 67)
      - Detroit Civic Affairs (Box 67)
      - Detroit Public Library (Box 67)
      - Detroit Street Railway (Box 67)
      - Disc Jockeys (Box 67)
      - Discrimination, 2 folders (Box 67)
      - Discrimination Within United Community Services (Box 67)
      - Drugs (Box 67)
      - Education
        - General, 4 folders (Box 67)
        - Detroit Public Schools, decentralization (Box 67)
        - Detroit Public Schools, high school survey, 5 folders (Box 68)
        - Detroit Public Schools, region I (Box 68)
        - Detroit Public Schools, region V (Box 68)
        - Incoming Communications (Box 68)
        - New Aspiration's Club (Box 68)
        - Racial Composition of Schools, 3 folders (Box 68)
        - Student aid, Butzel-Stevens Pope Fund, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - Student aid, National Urban League (Box 68)
        - Twelfth Street Academy (Box 68)
        - Urban Education Newsletter (Box 68)
        - Vocational Guidance (Box 68)
      - Employment
        - General, 3 folders (Box 68)
        - Patterns (Box 68)
        - Primary Resource List (Box 68)
        - Survey (Box 68)
        - Testing of Technical Aids (Box 68)
        - Training Proposal (Box 68)
      - Employment and Appointments in Municipal Government (Box 68)
      - Equal Opportunity Day 1964-1976, 13 folders (Box 69)
      - Evaluation of Detroit Urban League
        - 1943 (Box 69)
        - 1974 (Box 69)
      - Family Living, 4 folders (Box 69)
      - Fiftieth Anniversary Dinner 1966 (Box 69)
      - Fire (Box 69)
      - Forest Park Community College (Box 69)
      - General Motors Project (Box 69)
      - Health-Care
        - Greater Detroit Area Hospital Council, 3 folders (Box 69)
        - Hospitals (Box 69)
        - Hospital Discrimination (Box 69)
        - Hospital Survey, 2 folders (Box 69)
        - Hypertension (Box 69)
        - Licensure of Facilities (Box 69)
        - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 69)
        - Peoples Community Hospital Authority (Box 69)
        - Pre and Post Natal Care (Box 69)
        - Sickle Cell Anemia (Box 69)
        - Social Hygiene (Box 69)
        - Statistics (Box 69)
      - Health and Welfare Committee (Box 69)
      - Historical File
        - Correspondence 1916-1917 (Box 69)
        - Housing 1917 (Box 69)
        - Program Descriptions and Reports to 1970 (Box 69)
        - Speeches 1917-1918 (Box 69)
        - Cultural Projects (Box 69)
        - John C. Dancy Scrapbook (Box 69)
        - "The Negro in Michigan", 3 folders (Box 69)
        - Negro History (Box 69)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 69)
      - Housing
        - General (Box 70)
        - Apartment Breakthroughs (Box 70)
        - Medical Center Residents (Box 70)
        - Reports (Box 70)
      - Housing Assistant Reports (Box 70)
      - Housing Committee (Box 70)
      - Intergroup Relations (Box 70)
      - Illegitimacy (Box 70)
      - Membership Committee (Box 70)
      - Miscegenation (Box 70)
      - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 70)
      - National Catholic Conference for Inter-racial Justice (Box 70)
      - National Conference on Religion and Race (Box 70)
      - New Thrust Program, 2 folders (Box 70)
      - Organizations
        - Citizen's Concerns Committee (Box 70)
        - Concerned Citizens Council (Box 70)
        - CONGRO (Box 70)
        - Coordinating Council on Human Relations, 2 folders (Box 70)
        - Detroit Civic Rights Committee (Box 70)
        - Detroit Council of Organizations (Box 70)
        - Metropolitan Detroit Conference on Religion and Race (Box 70)
        - Michigan Civil Rights Commission (Box 70)
        - Michigan Voluntary Agency Group (Box 70)
        - Near East Side Coordinating Council (Box 70)
        - West Central Organizing Committee (Box 70)
      - Police
        - General (Box 71)
        - Citizens Committee for Human Relations (Box 71)
        - Neighborhood Workshop, 10th Precinct (Box 71)
        - Newspaperboys (Box 71)
        - S.T.R.E.S.S. (Box 71)
        - Training, 2 folders (Box 71)
      - Population Statistics
        - General (Box 71)
        - Mobility (Box 71)
        - Racial (Box 71)
      - Programs
        - 1940-1950 (Box 71)
        - 1967, 2 folders (Box 71)
      - Public and Community Affairs Task Force (Box 71)
      - Race Relations
        - General (Box 71)
        - 1941 (Box 71)
      - Racism (Box 71)
      - Religious Leaders (Box 71)
      - Religious Leadership Council 1967 (Box 71)
      - Research (Box 71)
      - Retired Senior Volunteer Program (Box 71)
      - Sears Seminar 1967 (Box 71)
      - Senior Citizens, 2 folders (Box 71)
      - Speakers Bureau (Box 71)
      - Study Report for United Fund (Box 71)